export const questions3 = [
  {
    question: 'Which star is the closest to Earth after the Sun?',
    options: ['Sirius', 'Vega', 'Proxima Centauri', 'Alpha Centauri A'],
    correctAnswer: 'Proxima Centauri',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which star is the brightest in the night sky?',
    options: ['Betelgeuse', 'Sirius', 'Rigel', 'Altair'],
    correctAnswer: 'Sirius',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which galaxy is closest to the Milky Way?',
    options: [
      'Large Magellanic Cloud',
      'Triangulum',
      'Andromeda',
      'Small Magellanic Cloud',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Andromeda',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the type of stars that emit radio waves at regular intervals?',
    options: ['Pulsars', 'Red Giants', 'Novas', 'White Dwarfs'],
    correctAnswer: 'Pulsars',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which star is a red giant located in the constellation Orion?',
    options: ['Sirius', 'Aldebaran', 'Polaris', 'Betelgeuse'],
    correctAnswer: 'Betelgeuse',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the galaxy in which Earth is located?',
    options: ['Milky Way', 'Andromeda', 'Large Magellanic Cloud', 'Sombrero'],
    correctAnswer: 'Milky Way',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the remnant of a supernova explosion?',
    options: ['Brown Dwarf', 'Neutron Star', 'Black Hole', 'Pulsar'],
    correctAnswer: 'Neutron Star',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the central part of a galaxy called, where many old stars are found?',
    options: ['Disk', 'Orbit', 'Core', 'Spiral Arms'],
    correctAnswer: 'Core',
  },
  {
    question: 'What process powers stars and gives them energy to shine?',
    options: [
      'Gravitational Compression',
      'Nuclear Fusion',
      'Chemical Burning',
      'Radioactive Decay',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Nuclear Fusion',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the huge collection of millions of stars, gas, and dust held together by gravity called?',
    options: ['Galaxy', 'Cluster', 'Planetary Nebula', 'Supernova'],
    correctAnswer: 'Galaxy',
  },
];
